Pappu Kar

UX/UI Designer

Projects

Backstore Pro / Aug 2022- Dec 2022

Link to the case study

Backstore Pro is an eCommerce mobile application where users will be able to buy quality products at the best price and conveniently.

- * Planned and conducted a study of relevant user requirements, incorporating data from case studies, personal interviews, and surveys.
- * Identified a clear set of problem statements inspired by user research as a guide for the overall project development.
- * Studied user analytics, constructively targeting and implementing required application components.

Shadow / Jan 2022- Apr 2022

Link to the case study

Shadow is a convenient movie reservation app that simplifies the seat reservation process. It's designed to be user-friendly and accessible from anywhere

- * Engaged in the initial prototyping process by conducting independent research on established case studies and drawing observations.
- * Established storyboards to brainstorm ideas and created a timeline to organize project objectives.
- * Designed prototypes in iterations using Figma to reflect continuous updates.

Experience

Digital Personal Shopper / Walmart

Sep 2022 - Present / Chamblee, Georgia

- * Picked quality and proper items for more than 200 orders per day.
- * Maintained close collaboration with store departments to ensure efficient service delivery.

Customer Service Representative / Publix Super Market

Feb 2016 - Dec 2021 / Tucker, Georgia

- * Executed 300+ product and service transactions daily using the Point-of-Sale system and other service registers.
- * Supplied excellent customer service and encouraged customers to purchase tickets for a chance to win up to \$500.

Education

Interdisciplinary Studies / Georgia State University

Expected May 2023 / Atlanta, Georgia

Computer Science / Georgia Perimeter College

Aug 2017 - May 2020 / Dunwoody, Georgia

Certifications & Training: Google UX Design Professional Certificate (in progress)

Contact

Atlanta, Georgia +17705723253

https://pappukar.com/

Pappukar806@yahoo.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/pappukar/

Skills

Research & Test

User interviews, Usability testings, Personas, Competitor analysis, User journeys

Design

User flows, Wireframes, Prototype, Site maps, Mockups, Responsive design

Other skills

HTML, CSS, SQL, Bengali (fluent), Hindi (conversational)

Tools

Research & Test

Zoom, Maze, Google meet, Microsoft Word, Microsoft Team

Design

Figma, FigJam, Adobe XD, Photoshop, Canva

Volunteer Experience

* Helped a nonprofit organization in preparing food and distributing meals to over 100 people 15 hours per week – Bornomala Association of Georgia.